<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sohan’s blog</title>
    <link>https://github.com/sohanrai09/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sohan’s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 18:02:41 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/sohanrai09/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Robotframework 1</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sohanrai09/blog/posts/robotframework-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 18:02:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://github.com/sohanrai09/blog/posts/robotframework-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In my new job role as a Test Engineer, knowing how to use Robot Framework for Automating Test Cases is crucial, to save time and to make testing more fun! As I&amp;rsquo;m going through this learning journey, I wanted to blog about it for anyone who is looking to start this journey and also to help me understand things in a better way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of good resources out there which explains the Robot Framework and it&amp;rsquo;s components. Best place to start would be the &lt;a href=&#34;https://robotframework.org/&#34;&gt;Robot Framework Documentation&lt;/a&gt;, which shows some interactive examples and very clear explaination. During my learning what I have come to realise is, there are lot of resources around Robot Framework used for Application Testing but there are not a lot of resources focused on Network Testing(or maybe I haven&amp;rsquo;t been thorough with my search!). That&amp;rsquo;s also one of the reaons for starting this blog, to give a Network Engineer&amp;rsquo;s perspective on Robot Framework and use the examples around networking to help us understand this better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
